 export const data = [
    {
      question: "What is the word for bird?\"",
      option1: "avila",
      option2: "orso",
      option3: "caballo",
      option4: "ucello",
      ans: 4,
    },
    {
      question: "What does \"mucca\" mean?",
      option1: "cow",
      option2: "dog",
      option3: "sheep",
      option4: "bear",
      ans: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "Which of the following means \"sheep\"?",
      option1: "peccora",
      option2: "pecorra",
      option3: "peccorra",
      option4: "pecora",
      ans: 4,
    },
    {
      question: "What does \"mela\" mean?",
      option1: "cake",
      option2: "cabbage",
      option3: "apple",
      option4: "pear",
      ans: 3,
    },
    {
      question: "What is the word for \"celery\"?",
      option1: "cedelio",
      option2: "sedano",
      option3: "mellaro",
      option4: "tosiaro",
      ans: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "Which of the following means \"cucumber\"?",
      option1: "curieno",
      option2: "cetriolo",
      option3: "cembiero",
      option4: "cuclioro",
      ans: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "Which of the following means \"shelf\"?",
      option1: "scaffale",
      option2: "scafalle",
      option3: "scaffalle",
      option4: "shafalle",
      ans: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "What does \"letto\" mean?",
      option1: "chair",
      option2: "bed",
      option3: "table",
      option4: "door",
      ans: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "What is the word for \"chair\"?",
      option1: "chelia",
      option2: "escrita",
      option3: "matita",
      option4: "sedia",
      ans: 4,
    },
    {
      question: "What is the word for \"paper\"?",
      option1: "pastallo",
      option2: "papel",
      option3: "carta",
      option4: "borsa",
      ans: 3,
    },
    {
      question: "What does \"matita\" mean?",
      option1: "backpack",
      option2: "pencil",
      option3: "marker",
      option4: "crayon",
      ans: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "Which of the following means \"crayon\"?",
      option1: "pastello",
      option2: "pastelo",
      option3: "penna",
      option4: "pena",
      ans: 1,
    },
  ];